(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
以心伝心ポーズチャレンジ！
Telepathy Pose Challenge!
お題は！
The theme is!
警察官
Police Officer
これ簡単！
This is easy!
あ、そうだよね！
Ah, right!
せーの！
Ready, set...
ほっ！
Hah!
は！？
Huh!?
なにそれ？
What is that?
敬礼！
A salute!
拳銃！
A handgun!
ねえ、おかしい！絶対違ってるよ！
Hey, that's weird! It's definitely different!
ドクター
Doctor
ドクター。
Doctor.
むずい。
Hard.
え、でもこれはもう、ね、あれしかない。
Eh, but for this, there's only one, right?
せーの！
Ready, set...
ほっ！
Hah!
は！？
Huh!?
え！？
Eh!?
何してんの？
What are you doing?
なんかさ、ネットでよくあるやつ。こうやってお医者さん...
Like, that thing common on the net. Like an eye doctor...
あ、運ぶやつ？
Ah, the carrying one?
うん、運ぶやつ。
Yeah, the carrying one.
ドクターかな？こっちでしょ。
Is that a doctor? It should be this.
聴診器？
A stethoscope?
あ、聴診器、聴診器。
Ah, a stethoscope, a stethoscope.
わかんないよ。
I don't know.
カメラマン
Cameraman
カメラマンもいま、いっぱいいっぱいあるからね。
There are many types of cameramen now.
せーの！
Ready, set...
ほっ！
Hah!
あああ！やった！
Aaaah! We did it!
やった！やっとだよ！
We did it! Finally!
お寿司屋さん
Sushi Shop
でもこれ、さすがにでしょ。
But this is a given, right?
せーの！
Ready, set...
ほっ！
Hah!
え？
Eh?
いや、おすしざんまい。
No, Sushizanmai.
寿司握ってる。
I'm making sushi.
はぁ！？
Hah!?
モデル
Model
えー？
Ehh?
でも大得意！
But I'm great at this!
せーの！
Ready, set...
ほっ！
Hah!
え？
Eh?
え、何かポーズした？
Eh, did you do a pose?
さあ、さあ。
Well, well...
以心伝心ポーズチャレンジ！お題は！
Telepathy Pose Challenge! The theme is!
バスケットボール
Basketball
予想してますよ。
I'm predicting it.
せーの！
Ready, set...
ほっ！
Hah!
やった！
We did it!
珍しく合ったぞ。
Rarely, we matched.
サッカー
Soccer
これどっちだろう？
I wonder which way this goes?
あ、待って、どっち、お前どっちだ？
Ah, wait, which way, which way are you going?
どっちだ、どっちだ！
Which way, which way!
せーの！
Ready, set...
はい！
Hah!
あああ！
Aaaah!
ゴールキーパー。
Goalkeeper.
え、自分もこれ、ゴールキーパー。
Eh, I'm also this, goalkeeper.
なんで下じゃないの？
Why isn't it down?
いや、上でしょ。
No, it's up.
野球
Baseball
これもどっちだ。
This is also which way.
せーの！
Ready, set...
はい！
Hah!
はい、無理。
Okay, impossible.
え、待って、でも合ってるよね？
Eh, wait, but we're matching, right?
でもさ、あれ、投げるのと受けるだよ。
But, like, one's throwing and the other's catching.
そう、投げる。
Yeah, throwing.
以心伝心は出来てないけど...
We didn't achieve telepathy, but...
チアリーディング
Cheerleading
チアリーディング。
Cheerleading.
あ、でもやったことある。
Ah, but I've done it before.
え、マジで？イメージでやるわ。
Eh, seriously? I'll do it by image.
行くよ。
Here I go.
せーの！
Ready, set...
ほっ！
Hah!
え、でも大体合ってね？
Eh, but aren't we mostly matching?
一緒じゃない？いいじゃん、いいじゃん。90%くらい。
Aren't we the same? Good, good. About 90%.
eスポーツ
eSports
ええ！？これってスポーツだっけ？
Ehh!? Is this a sport?
eスポーツだけど。
It's eSports, though.
せーの！
Ready, set...
ほっ！
Hah!
結局ね、パソコンだよね！
In the end, it's the PC, right!
パソコン見るしかないでしょ。めっちゃモニター近い。
You have to look at the PC. The monitor is so close.
以心伝心ポーズチャレンジ！お題は！
Telepathy Pose Challenge! The theme is!
アイドル
Idol
わかる！
I get it!
せーの！
Ready, set...
はい！
Hah!
え、一緒じゃない？
Eh, aren't we the same?
え、惜しくない？惜しい！
Eh, aren't we close? So close!
ボディビルダー
Bodybuilder
どれか。
One of them.
せーの！
Ready, set...
ほっ！
Hah!
ああ、無理。
Ah, impossible.
お笑い芸人
Comedian
はぁ？むずくね？
Huh? Isn't it hard?
せーの！
Ready, set...
はい！
Hah!
ツッコミ！出囃子！
The straight man! The entrance theme!
歴史上の偉人
Historical Great Figures
ええ、いっぱいいるって！
Ehh, there are so many!
誰が考えたの、これ？
Who thought of this?
プロデューサー。
The producer.
どうしようかな。
What should I do?
せーの！
Ready, set...
ほっ！
Hah!
え？
Eh?
それ誰？
Who is that?
わかんないけど偉そうな人。
I don't know, but someone important.
待って、吾輩もわかんないけど偉そうな人。
Wait, I don't know either, but someone important.
マインド一緒。
Our minds are the same.
考え方一緒。
Our way of thinking is the same.
殿
Lord
殿？え、殿？
Lord? Eh, lord?
わからん。
I don't know.
せーの！
Ready, set...
ほっ！
Hah!
さっきと一緒じゃん。
It's the same as before.
でもこれ、偉そうな殿。
But this is an important lord.
さっきとマインド一緒。
Same mind as before.
これは何？それ？
What's this? That?
吾輩はちょっと座ってる感じで。
I'm sort of sitting.
ヤンキー？
A delinquent?
違うよ！座ってるじゃん、殿は。
No! A lord is sitting, right?
以心伝心ポーズチャレンジ！お題は！
Telepathy Pose Challenge! The theme is!
猫
Cat
飼ってるしね。
I have one as a pet.
せーの！
Ready, set...
ほっ！
Hah!
なんだよ、それ！
What is that!
いや、これさ、玄関前待機してんのよ。
No, like, it's waiting in front of the entrance.
いや、猫って言ったらこれにゃんにゃんポーズでしょ。
No, if you say "cat", it's this "nyan-nyan" pose.
にゃんにゃん、そんなポーズやんねーよ！
Cats don't do "nyan-nyan" poses like that!
犬
Dog
これむず。
This is hard.
せーの！
Ready, set...
ほっ！
Hah!
あああ！めっちゃ合った！
Aaaah! We matched perfectly!
龍
Dragon
見たことないんだけど。
I've never seen one, though.
せーの！
Ready, set...
ほっ！
Hah!
これ、ドラゴンの手、短いでさ。
This, the dragon's hands are short, so...
女豹
Cougar
これはちょっと関係ありますよ。
This is a bit related.
せーの！
Ready, set...
ほっ！
Hah!
ああ、犬と一緒だって。
Ah, it's the same as the dog.
これむずい。
This is hard.
犬と一緒だろ、これ。
It's the same as the dog, right?
蝶々
Butterfly
一致すると思う。
I think we'll match.
せーの！
Ready, set...
ほっ！
Hah!
なんで閉じてんの？
Why is it closed?
ほらさ、手の、影のやつ。
Look, like, the hand shadow thing.
以心伝心ポーズチャレンジ！お題は！
Telepathy Pose Challenge! The theme is!
魔法少女
Magical Girl
あ、でもいっぱいいるよね。
Ah, but there are so many, right?
せーの！
Ready, set...
ほっ！
Hah!
杖持ってる。
I'm holding a wand.
魔法少女
Magical Girl
魔女っ子や。
It's a magical girl.
そっち少女じゃないよ。魔女だよ。
Yours isn't a girl. It's a witch.
え、嘘。
Wait, really?
天使
Angel
せーの！
Ready, set... go!
パラパラパーって。
Like, "para-para-pa."
痛い、意味わかんね。
Ouch, I don't get it.
小悪魔
Imp
あー、なんか分かるわ。
Ah, I kind of get it.
せーの！
Ready, set... go!
あ、待ってそれや！
Ah, wait, that's it!
え、これじゃない？
Eh, isn't it this?
うわそれだわ。
Whoa, that's the one.
マジでなにも浮かばなくて、ちょっとセクシーな感じ。
I really couldn't think of anything, so I went for a sexy vibe.
なにも浮かば...でも絶対これや。
I couldn't think... but it's definitely this.
怪盗
Phantom Thief
さっきこんなん見たから。
Because I saw something like this earlier.
せーの！
Ready, set... go!
待って、なにそれ。
Wait, what's that?
これ怪盗キッド様や。
This is Phantom Thief Kid.
うちも怪盗キッドや！
I'm also Phantom Thief Kid!
漫画家
Manga Artist
いろんなタイプいるからなあ。
There are all kinds of types.
せーの！
Ready, set... go!
うん、これはなんか、あの、ちょっと昔の漫画家さんイメージしてペン持ってる。
Yeah, this is like, uh, I'm holding a pen, imagining an old-school manga artist.
普通に書いてる人。
Just someone normally writing.
何のひねりもない。
No creativity at all.
何のひねりもない、ただのママ。
No creativity at all, just a mom.
だめだ、くっそー。
No good, damn it.
以心伝心ポーズチャレンジ！
Telepathy Pose Challenge!
お題は！
The theme is!
侍
Samurai
あー、やりがちなやつね。
Ah, the common one, right?
分かる。せーの！
I get it. Ready, set... go!
え、なにそれ。
Eh, what's that?
刀出して。
Drawing the sword.
あ、自分も抜刀。
Ah, I'm also drawing the sword.
似てるけど違う、くっそー。
Similar but different, damn it.
マジかよ、だめか。
Seriously? No good?
シャチ
Orca
あ、なにこれ。
Ah, what's this?
ルックスでくるわ。
I'll go with the look.
せーの！
Ready, set... go!
え、マジなにそれ。
Eh, seriously, what is that?
これシャチのなんか、角...
This is like the orca's... horn...
あ、頭の部分だった。
Ah, it was the head part.
コヨーテ
Coyote
いや、いいや。想像でいくよ。
No, it's fine. I'll go with my imagination.
せーの！
Ready, set... go!
これでしか合わねえじゃねえかよ。
That's the only way it would match, isn't it?
鷹
Hawk
せーの！
Ready, set... go!
羽です、羽です。
Wings, wings.
いっしょ！羽です！
Same! Wings!
秘密結社の総帥
Leader of Secret Society
はい。え、なんか、どれだろう。
Okay. Uh, I wonder which one.
分かるだろ、隣にいるだろ。
You should know, I'm right next to you.
せーの！
Ready, set... go!
え、いっしょじゃない？
Eh, aren't we the same?
刮目せよ！
Take heed!
以心伝心ポーズチャレンジ！
Telepathy Pose Challenge!
お題は！
The theme is!
ヨガ
Yoga
え、いっぱいあるぞ。
Eh, there are so many.
せーの！
Ready, set... go!
そっちか！
That one?!
可愛いポーズ
Cute Pose
ちょっと楽しみだな。いくよ。
I'm a bit excited. Here we go.
せーの！
Ready, set... go!
「え？」じゃない。可愛いだろ。
Don't "eh" me. It's cute, right?
逃げたね、逃げたね。
You ran away, didn't you?
セクシーなポーズ
Sexy Pose
せーの！
Ready, set... go!
うわ、ちょっとそれテクすぎだって。
Whoa, that's a bit too technical.
なんで！脇と胸見せるんだよ！
Why?! You're supposed to show your armpits and chest!
浅いんだからちょっと合わして。
You're being shallow, match me a bit.
ツンデレ女子
Tsundere Girl
あ、こんなん...
Ah, something like this...
せーの！
Ready, set... go!
はっ、待って、腕組んでる！
Ha, wait, you're crossing your arms!
いっしょ、いっしょ！やったー！
Same, same! Yay!
あざといポーズ
Calculatedly Cute Pose
はっ？可愛いポーズといっしょだろ。
What? It's the same as a cute pose.
いっしょ、いっしょ。せーの！
Same, same. Ready, set... go!
おいや、なにそれ。
Hey now, what's that?
足見せてる。えろ、えろ。
You're showing your leg. Lewd, lewd.
それは？えろ...ハート。
That one? Lewd... heart.
ハート？そう、えろポーズじゃなくて？
Heart? Yeah, not a lewd pose?
えろポーズじゃねえ、エナコのやつじゃねえ。
Not a lewd pose, it's not the Enako one.
そっちだろ、えろポーズ。
Yours is the lewd pose.
ただ風に揺られて
Just swaying in the wind,
何も考えずに
Without thinking about anything,
ただ雲を眺めて
Just gazing at the clouds,
過ごすのもいいわよね
Spending time like that is nice too, isn't it?
誰しも何かしら
Everyone is carrying
使命を抱えてる
Some kind of mission.
ただそれだけのこと
It's just as simple as that.
悩むのはもうやめた
I've stopped worrying about it.
さざ波の
Being healed by
音に癒やされてく
The sound of the ripples,
奇跡を運ぶ風の音
The sound of the wind that brings miracles,
時を閉じ込めて
Trapping time inside.
Shining star 綴れば
If I write down "Shining star,"
夢に眠る幻が
The phantom sleeping in my dreams
手のひらに降り注ぐ
Will pour into the palm of my hand.
新たな世界へ
To a new world.
I believe my sensation
果てしない道の向こうで
Beyond the endless road,
瞼の裏に映る
Reflecting on the back of my eyelids,
ひとしずくの光
Is a single drop of light.
ときめきを感じて
Feeling the heartbeat.
あなたが触れる全て
May everything you touch
幸せであるように
Be filled with happiness.
今生きる喜びを
So that I don't forget
忘れてしまわないように
The joy of living right now.
月の光
The moonlight,
隠す雲は揺らぎ
The clouds that hide it waver.
自由の翼は今も
The wings of freedom, even now,
大空を駆ける
Race through the vast sky.
Shining star 綴れば
If I write down "Shining star,"
夢に眠る幻が
The phantom sleeping in my dreams...
...イマジネーション
...imagination
魔法が使えるような
Like I could use magic
世界が広がる
A world unfolds
A believe of my sensation
今も降り積もる想いよ
Thoughts that keep piling up even now
切なさやときめきが
Sadness and excitement
心の真ん中で
At the center of my heart
熱いメロディになる
Become a hot melody
Shining star 包めば
If I wrap myself in a shining star
無限のイマジネーション
Infinite imagination
魔法が使えるような
Like I could use magic
世界が広がる
A world unfolds
A believe of my sensation
今も降り積もる想いよ
Thoughts that keep piling up even now
切なさやときめきが
Sadness and excitement
輝き出す
Begin to shine
Shining star 包めば
If I wrap myself in a shining star
夢に眠る幻が
The illusions sleeping in dreams
手のひらに降り注ぐ
Pour into my palm
新たな世界へ
Towards a new world
A believe of my sensation
果てしない道の向こうで
Beyond the endless road
瞼の裏に映る
Reflected behind my eyelids
ひとしずくの光
A single drop of light
ときめきを感じて
Feeling the excitement
La la la...
LADY / 作詞・作曲：米津玄師
LADY / Written & Composed by Kenshi Yonezu
例えば僕ら二人
For example, the two of us
煌めく映画のように
Like in a sparkling movie
出会い直せたらどうしたい
If we could meet again, what would you want to do?
何も謎めいてない
There's nothing mysterious
今日は昨日の続き
Today is a continuation of yesterday
日々は続くただぼんやり
Days continue just vaguely
微かな足音
Faint footsteps
知るはずのない場所
A place you're not supposed to know
それだけですべてわかってしまうよう
It feels like I understand everything just from that
見透かした嘘も
The lies I saw through
隠した本当も
And the truths I hid
そのすべて愛おしかった
All of it was precious
LADY 笑わないで聞いて
LADY, listen without laughing
Honey 見つめ合っていたくて
Honey, I want to keep looking at each other
君と二人
The two of us together
行ったり来たりしたいだけ
I just want to go back and forth
Baby 子供みたいに
Baby, like a child
恋がしたい
I want to fall in love
駆け散らしていく
Kicking up and scattering
僕らのストーリーライン
Our storyline
例えばどっちか一人
For example, if one of us
酷い不幸が襲い
Is struck by a terrible misfortune
二度と会えなくなったら
And we can never meet again
考えた矢先に
Just as I thought that
泣けてしまうくらい
So much that I almost cry
日々は続く急かしがちに
Days continue in a hurried way
いつもみたいな顔
A face like always
チープな戯言
Cheap nonsense
見過ごすようにまた優しいんだろう
You'll probably be kind again, as if overlooking it
見透かした嘘も
The lies I saw through
隠した本当も
And the truths I hid
その目から伝わってきた
They were conveyed through those eyes
引っ張ったり噛み付いたり
Pulling, biting
傷ついたふりしてみたり
Pretending to be hurt
明日の朝に持ち越したり
Carrying it over to tomorrow morning
浮ついたりして
Being restless
思い切り傷つきたい
I want to be hurt with all my might
いつまでもそばにいたい
I want to be by your side forever
今すぐ行方を眩まそう
Let's disappear right now
LADY 何も言わないで
LADY, don't say anything
HONEY 僕の手を獲ってくれ
HONEY, take my hand
君以外に考えられないだけ
It's just that I can't think of anyone else but you
BABY あの頃みたいに恋がしたい
BABY, I want to fall in love like back then
書き散らしてゆく
I'll keep scribbling
踊り続ける
And keep dancing
LADY 笑わないで聞いて
LADY, listen without laughing
HONEY 見つめ合っていたくって
HONEY, I want to keep looking at each other
君の隣に行ったり来たりしたいだけ
I just want to go back and forth by your side
BABY 子供みたいに恋がしたい
BABY, I want to fall in love like a child
書き散らしてゆく
I'll keep scribbling away
僕らのストーリーライン
Our storyline
うーい！うわー！ライブが始まっておるぞ！
U-i! Uwah! The live has begun!
誕生日！誕生日！いぇーい！
My birthday! My birthday! Yay!
ありがとー来てくれて！
Thank you for coming!
ということで！今日の配信のハッシュタグは
#ラプ様と愉快な仲間たち！
So! The hashtag for today's stream is
#Lap-samaAndFunnyFriends!
ということで、もちろんゲストがたくさん来るってことー！
Which means, of course, many guests will be coming!
ということで、そんじゃ行きます！
So, here we go!
以心伝心ポーズチャレンジ！
Ishindenshin Pose Challenge!
お題は？お題は？
The topic is? The topic is?
お題：イケメン
Topic: Handsome man
え、ちょっと待って？
Eh, wait a minute?
せーのっ！
Ready, go!
おいおいおいおい！
Oi oi oi oi!
えなこさんそれも…！？ え？
Enako-san, is that even...!? Eh?
いや、待って。私は「キラン」ってやったの。 あー。
No, wait. I did a "sparkle" pose. Ah.
それイケメンじゃなくてもいいじゃん！
That doesn't have to be a handsome man!
これイケメンだよ！絶対イケメン！
This is a handsome man! Definitely a handsome man!
え、待って、壁ドン？
Wait, "Kabedon"?
こういうさ、相撲みたいなポーズやってるのかと思った。
I thought you were doing a pose like sumo or something.
はぁ！？壁ドンだわボケ！
Hah!? It's "Kabedon", you idiot!
いや、だからね、やっぱりラプ様はイケメンのジャンルで
やっぱ違ったか。
No, I mean, as expected, Lap-sama's genre of
"handsome man" was different after all.
お、黙れ！
O- Shut up!
天上天下繋ぐ花火かな
Are those fireworks connecting heaven and earth?
万代と刹那の出会い
忘るまじ忘るまじ忘るまじ
A meeting of eternity and a moment,
never forget, never forget, never forget...
我等の夏を
Our summer...
長く短い祭
A Long and Short Festival
場違いに冷え切った身体を一頻りに放って流し
Leaving my out-of-place, chilled body to its own devices...
流され思えば遠くへ来たもんだ
And drifting along, I realize I've come quite far.
人生なんて飽気ないね まして若さはあっちゅう間
Life is so fleeting, and youth even more so.
今宵全員が魁 一枚目よ
Tonight, everyone is a pioneer, the lead actor.
皆銘々取り取りの衣装 奔放な命を化粧
Everyone in their own varied costumes, dressing up their unrestrained lives.
隠すまじ隠すまじ隠すまじ 我等の夏を
Never hide, never hide, never hide... our summer.
何某か白落ち込んだ心は一頻りに彷徨って流し
Leaving my somehow dejected heart to wander and drift...
流され思えば遠くへ来たもんだ
And drifting along, I realize I've come quite far.
永遠なんて素っ気ないね 仄な仮初めがいいね
Eternity is so indifferent; a faint, fleeting moment is better.
愈々饗宴も酣 本番です
Finally, the feast is at its peak; it's the main event.
皆銘々より取り見取り 喧騒な命を休め
Everyone chooses their favorite, resting their noisy lives.
隠すまじ隠すまじ隠すまじ 我等の夏を
Never hide, never hide, never hide... our summer.
ちょいと女盛りをどうしよう このままじゃ行き場がない
Wait, what should I do with my prime? At this rate, there's nowhere to go.
花盛り 色盛り 真盛り まだ
In full bloom, in full color, at the peak... still.
丁度宵の枝垂れ柳 蘇る人世の走馬灯
The weeping willow of the evening, a kaleidoscope of human life revived.
長く短い祭
Long and Short Festival
そう
So
逃すまじ逃すまじ逃すまじ
Don't let it slip, don't let it slip, don't let it slip
我らの夏を
Our summer
ちょいと
Just a bit
あちょいと
Oh, just a bit
女盛りをどうしよう
What should I do with my prime?
このままじゃまだ終われないわ
I can't let it end like this yet
花盛り 盛り 正盛り ああ まだまだ
In full bloom, in the prime, truly in the prime, ah, not yet, not yet
さようなら、はじめまして
Goodbye, nice to meet you
わっ、そーみ！
Whoa, So-mi!
やば、マジで、おい、こんな初めてだよ！
That was crazy, seriously, man, this is a first for me!
来てくれてありがとね！
Thanks for coming!
ありがとう！めっちゃ楽しかったわ！クソ楽しい、マジで！
Thank you! That was so much fun! It's so much fun, seriously!
そーみだってさ、いるんだもん、ステージに。すごくない？
Because even So-mi is here on stage. Isn't that amazing?
ありがとう、こんな舞台に立たせてくれて。こんな俺は経験をすると思ってなかったよ。
Thank you for letting me stand on a stage like this. I never thought I'd experience something like this.
ありがとね、来てくれて。
Thank you for coming.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
初めて絡んだの、いつか覚えてますか？
Do you remember when we first interacted?
あれだよね、いや、俺は覚えてるよ。あの、俺が普通に平和に Rust をしていたら...
It was that, right? Yeah, I remember. Um, when I was playing Rust normally and peacefully...
うんうん。
Yeah, yeah.
...なんか現れて、ガキんちょが。
...this kid suddenly appeared.
僕の土地をさ、奪っていってさ...
And then she took over my land...
ちょ、ちがっ...
Hey, that's not...
勝手にね、商売始めたんだよね。
...and started a business on her own, right?
違う、借りたの、借りたの！貸してくれるって...
No, I borrowed it! You said you'd lend it...
...言ったって、俺！
...you said so yourself!
もう分捕られたみたいな、俺の店、居抜きでさ。
It was like it was snatched away, you took over my whole shop.
違う、貸してくれて！
No, you lent it to me!
しかも、あの、業務手伝ってくれた。
And you even helped out with the business.
業務手伝ってくれた... ほぼパシリだったけどな。
You 'helped out'... I was basically your errand boy.
お前が作ったボイスの在庫を補充する係をしてたんだ、俺は。
I was the one in charge of restocking the voice packs you made.
毎回、毎回、えーそーみこれ売ってくれって、はい、分かりました、売らせていただきますって。
Every single time, it was 'Hey So-mi, sell this for me,' and I'd be like, 'Yes, I understand, I'll sell it.'
俺、補充してたんだよ。
I was the one restocking them.
いやもうマジで爆売れだったよ！ありがとね！
No, seriously, they sold like crazy! Thanks!
爆売れだったな、あれは。
They really did sell like crazy.
最近は？
And recently?
最近は、でもあれじゃない？やっぱりあの、VCR GTA を一緒にやったのがデカかったね。
Recently, wasn't it that? Doing VCR GTA together was a big deal.
あ、GTA！
Ah, GTA!
そうだね、初めて同じチームになってさ。
Right, that was the first time we were on the same team.
マジ全然やんねえじゃん、LoL。
You seriously never play LoL.
俺はあれで、あれじゃないの？
With that, isn't it...?
いろんな仲を深めて、僕があなたに LoL を教えた感じ...
We deepened our bond, and I taught you how to play LoL...
あ、そう？ え、LoLって何ですか？
Oh, really? Uh, what's LoL?
は？ は？
What? What?
お前、あんだけ俺がし、親身に教えたよね、君に！
You! I taught you so kindly and carefully!
Lo- LoL?
そうだよ！
Yes!
LoL?
LoL ってゲームがあったよ！もうなくなっちゃった？記憶から。
There was a game called LoL! Has it already disappeared? From your memory.
なんだっけ？
What was it?
やば、わかんない。けど...
Oh no, I don't know. But...
あったんだよ、君は頑張って、俺、君が頑張ってたの覚えてる。
It existed! You worked hard at it, I remember you working hard.
頑張ってないよ。
I didn't work hard.
頑張ってたよ！
You did!
頑張ってないし。やめろよ。
I didn't. Stop it.
お前のせいでなんか最近風評被害がやばい。
Because of you, the rumors lately have been crazy.
お前が発端だよ、てか。
You're the one who started it, actually.
こいつが！こいつのせいです！
This guy! It's his fault!
営業妨害です！
It's business interference!
この人すぐチャット晒すんで、みんなチャット送らないほうがいいです！
This person exposes chats right away, so everyone shouldn't send him chats!
いや、あんないっぱい来たら晒したくなっちゃうよね！
Well, if that many come, you just want to expose them!
やめて、ちょっと待って！誰も晒してないよ！
Stop it, wait a minute! No one is exposing anything!
あの、晒す人いないから！
Um, because there's no one to expose!
あ、そうなの？
Oh, really?
そうだよ！
Yes!
今後は気をつけます。
I'll be careful in the future.
はい、よろしい。ありがとね、歌ってくれて。
Okay, good. Thanks for singing with me.
ありがとうございました、本当に。
Thank you very much, truly.
いやでもちょっとね、カメラ目線面白い。
But wait, the way you look at the camera is funny.
なんで！
Why!
他のやる人より、俺はこう、カメラ目線どんどん...
More than other people, I'm just going to keep looking at the camera...
やめて、あぶい、マジでいいって！もう終わりますから。
Stop it, it's dangerous, seriously, enough! We're finishing now.
終わりです、バイバイ！
We're done, bye-bye!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ハイ、そーみバイバイ。ありがとね。頑張ってね。応援してるよ。
Okay, bye-bye So-mi. Thanks. Good luck. I'm rooting for you.
頑張ります！バイバイ！
I'll do my best! Bye-bye!
以心伝心ポーズチャレンジ
Isshin Denshin Pose Challenge
以心伝心ポーズチャレンジ！
Isshin Denshin Pose Challenge!
お題 VTuber
Theme: VTuber
お題は、VTuber！
The theme is, VTuber!
えー！むずっ！
What! That's hard!
待って！これ？
Wait! This?
せーの！
Ready, go!
ガチでなに？ガチでなに？
Seriously, what? Seriously, what?
御社の、マリン船長や！
It's your company's Marine-senchou!
マリン船長のポーズ。いや、お前が変な格好してんだよ！
Marine-senchou's pose. No, you're the one making a weird pose!
全然違うよ！ラプラス様は？
It's totally different! What about you, La+?
これ VTuber があの、配信終わりやるやつ。
This is what VTubers do at the end of their streams.
なにそれ？
What's that?
バイバイ〜って。
Like, 'Bye-bye~'.
ああ〜、おつぷる〜って。おつぷる...
Oh, like 'Otsupuru~'. Otsupuru...
わかんないよ！むずい。
I don't know! It's hard.
INTERNET OVERDOSE
天鬼ぷるる
Amaki Pururu
空想 幻想 三次元 インターネット 照らし出す たった一つの光
Fantasy, illusion, 3D. The Internet shines, the one and only light
赤見かるび
Akami Karubi
電子の海を漂うオタクに笑顔を
Giving smiles to the otakus drifting in the electronic sea
橘ひなの
Tachibana Hinano
未来は平和お約束 総務省だけど任せとけ
Peace for the future is a promise. It's the Ministry of Internal Affairs, but leave it to me
インターネット・エンジェル ただいま降臨
Internet Angel, descending now
INTERNET OVERDOSE
作詞: にゃるら 作曲: Aiobahn
Lyrics: Nyarura Composition: Aiobahn
社会をやめろ
Quit society.
家族をやめろ
Quit your family.
人間関係をやめろ
Quit human relationships.
今すぐ薄暗い部屋に
Right now, in a dim room,
青白いライトを浴びろ
bask in the pale blue light.
大丈夫
It's okay.
怖かったこと全部上書きするからね
I'll overwrite everything that was scary, okay?
狂い喫せり (Crazy for you)
Indulging in madness (Crazy for you).
おかしくなりそうなほど情報過多のインターネット
An information-overloaded internet that's driving me crazy.
おたすけしてあげるよダーリンダーリン
I'll save you, darling, darling.
うさ耳カチューシャ、ピンク染めの髪、媚薬ボソッ　しあわせ
Bunny ears, pink-dyed hair, aphrodisiac whisper... happiness.
壊れてしまうけど
Though it's breaking...
考えなくていいんだよ
You don't have to think anymore.
もうすぐ楽になるから
It'll be easier soon.
周りのみんながはしゃぐ毒ベリー
Everyone around us is frolicking, poison berry.
麻薬より甘いよ
It's sweeter than narcotics.
いいね　よくないね　君にとっては毒だね
Like, not like. To you, it's poison.
いいね　よくないね　それゲームオーバーだね
Like, not like. That's a game-over problem.
いいね　よくないね　二人だけの秘密だね
Like, not like. It's a secret just for the two of us.
私だけ見ててね
Just look at me.
まるで天使のように微笑む
Just like an angel, with a faint smile,
強めな劇薬　インターネット
a strong-flavored internet.
かざして悪魔のように囁く
Just like a devil, whispering,
あなただけのデパスがある
only your days exist.
浅い眠りと承認欲求のオーバードーズ
Overdose of shallow sleep and recognition desire.
脳天直撃する私たちだけの宗教と光
The religion and light of just us, whose brainstems are vibrating.
倫理より激しく脳中枢を浸食する恋
A love that invades the brain more intense than ethics.
何度も送られる電波、優しき毒の寸で
Non-stop repeated pleasure, through a gentle needle.
逆さまのコンピューターと断片的なカウンセリング
Upside-down computer and fragmentary counseling.
きらめく執着に耳心地いい旋律
Glittering obsession, melody that's nice to the ears.
夕暮れ時にさよならの練習をして
Practicing saying goodbye at sunset.
壊して　愛して　狂って　狂って　甘く狂わせて
Break it, love it, go crazy, go crazy, sweeten it.
ゆらぎはじめる世界
The world starting to waver.
あいまいになる風景
The scenery becoming vague.
あなただけ写しているメロディ
Only you are reflected in this melody.
神様なんていないよ
There is no God.
このふざけたインターネット、七色のサイケデリック
This messed up internet, seven-colored psychedelic.
SNSという名の水銀地獄に救済を！
Salvation in the SNS maze hell!
過去の歴史や未来、あなたのためなら飛んでいく
Past history or future, if it's for you, let's fly together.
インターネットエンジェル、可愛く参上！
Internet Angel, descending with a pose!
まるで天使のように抱きつく
Just like an angel, holding you tight,
強めな劇薬　インターネット
a strong-flavored internet.
かざして悪魔のように気絶する
Just like a devil, fainting,
あなただけのデパスがある
only your days exist.
エンジェル...
Angel...
わー、みんなー、うおー、ぺらぺらだねー！
Whoa, everyone! Whoa, you're all so paper-thin!
うわー、ぺらぺらだねー
Whoa, so paper-thin.
わーい！
Yay!
ぺらぺらだねー
Paper-thin, right.
ありがとう、呼んでくれて
Thank you for inviting us.
そうなんだよー、見て見てちょっと横向いて
That's right! Look, look, turn to the side for a bit.
はい！
Yes!
はははは！ぺらぺらだー
Hahaha! You're paper-thin!
やめてー
Stop it!
ありがとうー、でも呼んでくれたから出れたんだよ、ありがとう
Thank you... but I could only appear because you called me, so thank you.
ありがとうー
Thank you!
嬉しいね、ぺらぺらでも嬉しいよ
I'm happy. Even if you're paper-thin, I'm happy.
嬉しいよー
It's happy!
いつかさー、立体的に、なってきてほしいよね
I hope you'll become 3D-ish someday.
いつかね
Someday, right?
そうだねー
立体的に、なれたらいいんだけど、吾輩はいけるんだけど、なぜか紙...
I wish we could become 3D, and I can actually do it, but for some reason I'm paper...
そう、吾輩はね、今回はね、やっぱ紙...
Yeah, for me, this time, I'm paper after all...
なんで？なんで紙なの？
Why? Why paper?
え、二人が紙だからじゃない？
Isn't it because you two are paper?
合わせてきてくれた？
To match us?
合わせて、くれたの？
嬉しい！うちらと一緒に立体になろう！
Happy! Let's become 3D together with us!
次、立体になってきてくださいよー
Please become 3D next time!
え、みんなさー、吾輩と初めて会った時のこと覚えてる？
Do you remember when we first met?
ぷるるさんは？
Pururu-san?
覚えてます！ヴァロラントです！
I remember! Valorant!
そうだね！
Right!
ひなのちゃんは？
Hinano-chan?
いや、私ももちろん覚えてるよ。ヴァロラントでしょ？
Of course I remember. Valorant, right?
え、ヴァロラントだねー
Valorant, right.
そらちゃんは？
Sora-chan?
お、私はー、ストサバかな？
I... maybe from Stosaba (Rust Survival)?
ストサバ？
Stosaba?
この人だけヴァロじゃありません！
Only this person isn't Varo!
なんで私だけストサバなのー
Why only me not Varo!?
でも、いっぱいやったもんね、らぷちゃんとはね
But we played a lot together, didn't we, Lapu-chan?
いやーマジお前しかランク回してないからさ
Seriously, you're the only one I play ranked with.
しゃーなしお前、しゃーなしお前ね
I had no choice but you. No choice but you.
しゃーなしって言わないでー
Don't say 'no choice'!
で、さらに下にぷるるがいて、上がれば、ひなのとかな、神だからね！
And further down is Pururu, and then Hinano... you're a god!
いやいやお前！
No way, you!
なかなかできないからね、神、絶対神だもん
It's not easy to become one. You're definitely a god.
そんなことないよー
That's not true.
今？
Now?
今、プラチナとか。
Now, like Platinum rank.
ぜ、絶対いけないもん！
N-No way I can get there!
そんなことないよ！
That's not true!
ブロンズです。
I'm Bronze.
シルバーですら行けません。
I can't even get to Silver.
この時点で行けないんですよ。
I can't get there at this stage.
でも最近はあれでしょ？GTA。
But recently it's that, right? GTA.
そうだね。
Yeah.
GTAね。絡みといえばGTA。
GTA, right. When it comes to interactions, it's GTA.
あとアイコスクイズ。
And the Ico Quiz.
あの謎のクイズね。
That mysterious quiz.
マジでおもろかったから。
It was seriously funny.
わかんないと言いながら...
While saying you didn't know...
大無双してたけど。
You were totally dominating.
ぷるるがいたの覚えてたんだけどさ...
I remembered Pururu was there...
かるびがクイズにいたの忘れてたんだよね。
But I forgot Kalbi was in the quiz.
ひどくない！？
Isn't that mean!?
俺、かるびいたっけ？って。
I was like, "Wait, was Kalbi there?"
本当にひどい！いたっけって...
That's really mean! "Was she there"...
こいつ吾輩の給料聞いてきたこと思い出してさ。
I remembered this guy asking about my salary.
やめて！
Stop it!
車の直しをしてくれた...
He fixed my car...
直したね。
Yeah, he fixed it.
昨日の時もめっちゃ呼ばれてたけど。
I was being called a lot yesterday too.
マジで太客だった。
You were seriously a big customer.
相当呼ばれたもんな。
I really got called out a lot.
よく壊すから。
Because I break it often.
気をつけてということで。
So be careful.
みんなピンクとか赤じゃん。
Everyone is pink or red.
そうだね。
That's right.
吾輩だけ紫。
I'm the only purple one.
逆に目立っていいよね、主役ですから。
Conversely, it's good because I stand out, since I'm the main character.
みんな、吾輩に「誕生日おめでとう」お願いします！
Everyone, please wish me a happy birthday!
せーのってする？
Should we do a "ready, set"?
お願いします。せーの！
Please. Ready, set!
誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
バラバラだなぁ...
Everyone is out of sync...
これからも頑張るんで、応援してください！
I'll keep working hard, so please support me!
ラプ様頑張れ...
Go La+-sama...
ちっちゃい声！
Such a small voice!
もう行きます！バイバーイ！
I'm going now! Bye-bye!
以心伝心ポーズチャレンジ！
Telepathy Pose Challenge!
お題：蛇
Topic: Snake
これはいけるんじゃないか？
Don't you think we can do this?
せーの！
Ready, go!
え、それ沸かしてた今？
Wait, were you boiling it just now?
クネクネクネ...
Wiggle wiggle wiggle...
吾輩も、クネクネクネ...
I was wiggle wiggle wiggle too...
残念！
Unfortunate!
夢ならばどれほどよかったでしょう
If it were a dream, how good it would have been
未だにあなたのことを夢にみる
Even now, I dream about you
忘れた物を取りに帰るように
Like returning to retrieve something forgotten
古びた思い出の埃を払う
Dusting off old memories
戻らない幸せがあることを
That there is a happiness that will never return
最後にあなたが教えてくれた
Is what you taught me at the very end
言えずに隠してた暗い過去も
The dark past I hid without being able to say
あなたがいなきゃ永遠に暗いまま
Would remain dark forever without you
きっともうこれ以上傷つくことなど
Surely, being hurt any more than this
ありはしないとわかっている
Is something that I know will not happen
あの日の悲しみさえ
Even the sadness of that day
あの日の苦しみさえ
Even the pain of that day
そのすべてを愛してたあなたとともに
I loved all of it, together with you
胸に残り離れない苦いレモンの匂い
The bitter scent of lemon that stays in my heart
雨が降り止むまでは帰れない
I can't go home until the rain stops
今でもあなたは私の光
Even now, you are my light
暗闇であなたの背をなぞった
I traced your back in the darkness
その輪郭を鮮明に覚えている
I remember that silhouette clearly
受け止めきれないものと出会うたび
Every time I encounter something I can't handle
溢れてやまないのは涙だけ
The only thing that won't stop overflowing are tears
何をしていたの
What were you doing?
何を見ていたの
What were you looking at?
私の知らない横顔で
With a profile that I didn't know
どこかであなたが今私と同じような
If you are somewhere now, just like me
涙にくれ寂しさの中にいるなら
In the midst of loneliness and tears
私のことなどどうか忘れて
Then please, somehow forget about me
...ください
...please.
そんなこと心から願うほどに
So much so that I pray for it from my heart
今でもあなたはわたしの光
Even now, you are my light.
自分が思うより
More than I thought,
恋をしていたあなたに
I was in love with you.
あれから思うように
Since then, as I wished,
息ができない
I can't breathe.
あんなにそばにいたのに
Even though you were so close,
まるで嘘みたい
It's like a lie.
とても忘れられない
I can never forget.
それだけが確か
That alone is certain.
あの日の悲しみさえ
Even the sadness of that day,
あの日の苦しみさえ
even the pain of that day.
そのすべてを愛してた あなたとともに
I loved all of it, along with you.
雨が降り止むまでは帰れない
I can't go home until the rain stops.
切り分けた果実の片方の様に
Like one half of a sliced fruit,
今でもあなたは私の光
even now, you are my light.
だ、だ、だ、だ、蛇足！！
D-D-D-D-Dasoku!!
はいはいはい。
Yes, yes, yes.
え、ちょっとテンション...
Eh, a bit high tension...
テンション高いね。
You're high energy.
低いですよ！元気だね。
I'm low! You're energetic.
あー、今日ライブなんですよ。誕生日なんですよ。
Ah, today's a live. It's my birthday.
ああ、おめでとうございます。それに関しては。
Ah, congratulations. On that note.
ありがと。え、初絡みいつですか？覚えてます？
Thanks. When was our first collab? Remember?
覚えてますよ。あれですよ。VALORANTね。
I remember. It was that. Valorant.
本当に？覚えてる？
Really? You remember?
VALORANTじゃないの？違う？
Wasn't it Valorant? No?
あ、あの、けんきが誘ってくれて。
Ah, Kenki invited us.
そうそうそう。
Right, right, right.
それね。懐かしいね。
That. How nostalgic.
そこから...
From there...
そのあと、GTAかな？
After that, GTA maybe?
ちょっとないか。
Maybe not?
GTAでなんか彷徨ってたから。
Because you were wandering around in GTA.
彷徨ってない。
I wasn't wandering.
え、寂しいのかと思って。「蛇足だー！」って一緒にチームになったり。
I thought you might be lonely. "It's Dasoku!" and we teamed up.
VCRにして、そこから。
In VCR, from there.
楽しい日々を送ったね。
We had some fun days.
本当に思ってる？
Do you really mean it?
思ってるよ。
I do.
思ってないじゃん。
You don't.
見てこれ。
Look at this.
ちゃんとGTAのやつ着てる。
I'm wearing the GTA one.
あー、思い出。たまたまだけど。
Ah, memories. It's a coincidence though.
たまたま... え、着てきてくれたのかと思ったよ。
Coincidence... Eh, I thought you wore it for me.
雑杯の前にさ、VALORANT、プルルと3人でやったの覚えてる？
Before Zappai, remember we played Valorant with Pururu?
覚えてる。意味わかんなかったけどあの3人。
I remember. I didn't get that trio though.
深夜に雑に誘ってやったんだけど、
I invited you guys casually late at night,
その時にみんなVCつけてたのに、なぜか蛇足だけバレた。
and everyone had VC on, but for some reason only Dasoku was caught.
そうだよね。
That's right.
「蛇足さんですか？」って。
Like "Are you Dasoku-san?"
2人ともまあまあ特徴ある声なのにさ。
Even though both of us have pretty distinctive voices.
蛇足だけバレて。
Only Dasoku got caught.
その時野良にさ、「レモン歌ってください」って。
And the random player asked, "Please sing Lemon."
意味わかんないよね。
It was weird.
だから、あ、じゃあ歌おうと思って呼んだ。
So, I thought, "Okay, let's sing it," and invited you.
そこが？じゃあその野良の人のおかげでこれがあったの？
That's it? So this happened thanks to that random player?
すごいね。
That's amazing.
ありがとね。
Thanks.
あの時のあの人。
That person from that time.
このスタジオに全然似合わなくていい。
It's nice how you totally don't fit in this studio.
そんなことないでしょ。
That's not true.
あるだろ。
It is.
歌い手ですから元々。
I'm originally an utaite.
確かに。
True.
本当にストリーマーだと思ってて。
I really thought you were a streamer.
元々有名歌い手ですよ。
I'm originally a famous utaite.
有名ストリーマーかと思ってたんだけど。
I thought you were a famous streamer.
歌上手だもん。
You're good at singing.
歌でやってきましたから。15年くらい。
I've been doing music for about 15 years.
え、すご！
Eh, amazing!
お歌3周年、3年目。
My 3rd anniversary.
5倍。
5 times as long.
はい、次があるんで。
Okay, there's a next part.
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
雑だな、一生。
So casual, always.
バイバイバイバイ！
Bye-bye bye-bye!
以心伝心ポーズチャレンジ！！
Ishinden-Shin Pose Challenge!!
お題は... アーティスト！！
The theme is... Artist!!
え、むず！！
Eh, hard!!
誰が考えてるんだこれ。
Who thought of this?
あ、うちのプロデューサーです。
Ah, it's my producer.
すみません。
Sorry.
せーの！
Ready, go!
お題：アーティスト
Theme: Artist
え？ え？
Eh? Eh?
何それ？ ちょっと待って
What's that? Wait a sec.
え、マイク持って、手、上げてる？
Wait, are you holding a mic and raising your hand?
そう、私が一人なんだけど...
Yeah, though I'm all alone...
いや、久しぶりにハッハッ...
No, it's been a while, haha...
やっと、やっと会えたー！
Finally, finally we met!
Easy Breezy
作詞：Rachel / Mamiko 作曲：Rachel / Mamiko / ryo takahashi
Lyrics: Rachel / Mamiko Composer: Rachel / Mamiko / ryo takahashi
Easy Breezy
Daoko
はい、始まった、絡まった、辛かった
Yes, it started, got tangled, it was tough
奴らはどこかに行っちゃった
Those guys went somewhere else
誰に頼まれたわけでもないのに　止まらぬ筆
Even though no one asked me to, the pen doesn't stop
ここでは誰もが王様なのね
Everyone is a king here, right?
我儘が長続きする気がしない
I don't think selfishness will last long
どこかその性格で何が悪い
What's wrong with having that personality?
好きなもんは好き、外野はおだまり
I like what I like, outsiders shut up
君無責任、ここ地上のグラビティ
You're irresponsible, the gravity here on earth
さあさあ、お邪魔しないでね
Now then, don't get in the way
一発、派手にやってみようや
Let's give it a go, flashily
飲み込もうイマジネーション
Let's swallow the imagination
見たもん、聞いたもん、それ全部
What I saw, what I heard, all of it
気になるとべ、とべ、なめさすどけ
If you're curious, fly, fly, make them lick it, move
頭の中も完成形見えた
I can see the final form in my head
頭の中も自由自在
In my head, it's also free and flexible
心の網目細かくして
Make the mesh of your heart fine
最強の世界できちゃってるわな
The strongest world is already being built
いっちょ、パッ、パッ、と決めて
Let's decide quickly, pop, pop
戦闘モードなんだこりゃ
It's battle mode, what is this?
どうせやるならめんどくさくなろうぜ
If we're gonna do it, let's get messy
何様にするのさ
Who do you think you are?
Easy Breezy
今さ、パッ、パッ、と決めたなら
Right now, if you've decided quickly, pop, pop
やったらいいじゃん、どんなもんだ
Then just do it, how about that?
破れかぶれでもどうにかこうにかしようぜ
Even if it's desperate, let's make it work somehow
何様にするのさ
Who do you think you are?
Easy Breezy
見切り発車で進んじまったね
We started without looking ahead
街の灯りが後ろに消えてく
The city lights are disappearing behind us
鼓動、手ぶらでもなるようになるのさ
Heartbeat, even empty-handed, things will work out
あら、あら、もうこんな時間
Ara, ara, it's already this time
腹減った、めっちゃラーメン食べたい
I'm hungry, I really want to eat ramen
I say, you say, はい、もっと待ってな
I say, you say, yes, wait a bit more
あっという間完成するなんて以外、満場、明けな
Finished in no time, except for that, full house
鳥鳴いてら
Birds are singing
こっちへおいでよ
Come over here
一面からは見せらんない
Can't show it from just one side
こっちへおいでよ
Come over here
ちゃんと自分で意識してみて
Try to be conscious of it yourself
ほらどんなもんかカッコつかないわ
Look, how is it? It's not cool
届く愛つな入れ歯（こいつがいれば）
Connecting love... (if he's here)
余裕だわ、牙なめの奴ら
It's easy, those with bared fangs
バチバチな気配、パラは満々、満々だ
Sparks flying atmosphere, ready to go
明日になれば変わんない、止まるつもりないわ
Won't change tomorrow, don't intend to stop
Easy Breezy
いっちょ、パッ、パッ、と決めて
Let's decide quickly, pop, pop
戦闘モードなんだこりゃ
It's battle mode, what is this?
どうせやるならめんどくさくなろうぜ
If we're gonna do it, let's get messy
何様にするのさ
Who do you think you are?
Easy Breezy
今さ、パッ、パッ、と決めたなら
Right now, if you've decided quickly, pop, pop
やったらいいじゃん、どんなもんだ
Then just do it, how about that?
答え分かってりゃ苦労なんてしないぜ
If I knew the answer, I wouldn't have any trouble
何様にするのさ
Who do you think you are?
Easy Breezy
はぁ、お疲れ様
Phew, good job.
Daoko...
ちょっと、代わりに言って、代わりに
Wait, you say it, you say it instead.
あ、まだ起き上がれてない
Ah, she hasn't been able to get up yet.
ラプラス様が...
La+ sama is...
おぎゃー！ おぎゃー！ 生まれる！
Ogya! Ogya! I'm being born!
仕方ない、MCパートが待ってますよ
Can't be helped, the MC part is waiting.
そうだね、MCだね
That's right, MC.
Daokoが苦手なMCだね
The MC that Daoko is bad at.
あー、やめてね
Ah, stop that.
何笑ってんだよ
What are you laughing at?
いや、うぶいなと思って
No, I just thought you're so fresh.
恥ずかしがっていらっしゃったなと思って
I thought you looked embarrassed.
嬉しかったんだよ
I was just happy.
だってさ、ずっと文通してたじゃん
Because, you know, we've been writing letters
to each other for a long time.
そうですね、文通友達
That's right, pen pals.
文通仲間
Pen pal buddies.
だから、今日初めて会ったよね
So, we met for the first time today, right?
今日初めてお会いしましたね
We met for the first time today.
なんか、嬉しがってる
Somehow, she's so happy.
体で表現して、可愛いですね
Expressing it with her body, it's cute.
吾輩が、Daoko、一緒に歌わないか？って言ったら
When I asked, "Daoko, want to sing together?"
突然ね
Suddenly, right?
やるやる！って言ってくれたから
"I'll do it, I'll do it!" you said.
来てくれてありがとうだわ
Thank you for coming.
いや、こちらこそありがとうございます
No, thank you as well.
いいでしょ、このステージかっこいいでしょ
Isn't it great? This stage is cool, isn't it?
あ、めちゃめちゃカッコいいステージに...
Ah, on such a cool stage...
ああ、本当だ。
Yeah, truly.
え、しかも今日衣装を合わせてきてくれたでしょ？
And you wore a matching outfit today, didn't you?
そうなんです。もうラプ様をイメージさせていただきました。
That's right. I based it on La-sama's image.
かわいいじゃん！
It's cute!
恐縮ながら...
I'm honored...
かわいいじゃんかよ！
It's so cute!
照れてる照れてる。
Blushing, blushing.
え、あのさ... 正直
Um, say... honestly,
はい？
Yes?
いい？
Is it okay?
え、何ですか？
Uh, what is it?
我輩のこと、好き？
Do you like me?
あ... えと、ラプさん...
Ah... Well, La-san...
なに？なに？
What? What?
あ、そろそろ... 時間じゃないですか？
Ah, isn't it... about time?
ごまかした！ごまかした！嘘でしょ？
She dodged it! She dodged it! No way?
言ってえよ！嘘！なんで？
Tell me! No! Why?
次行かないと。続きはウェブで。
We have to move on. The rest is on the web.
バカ！あー、知らない！
Stupid! Ah, I don't know!
以心伝心ポーズチャレンジ
Telepathy Pose Challenge
お題は...
The topic is...
ギャング
Gang
はぁー！
Haa!
これはお得意なんじゃない？
Isn't this our specialty?
なんでだよ！
Why would it be!
せーの！
One, two!
えー！？えー！？嘘でしょ？
Eh!? Eh!? No way?
何それ？
What's that?
え、なんか「オラァ」みたいなやつ。
Like a "Hey, you!" sort of thing.
あ、それヤンキーや。
Ah, that's a delinquent.
蛇足 / スタンミじゃぱん / けんき / うゆ / 天鬼ぷるる / しろまんた
Dasoku / Stanmi Japan / Kenki / Uyu / Amaki Pururu / Shiromanta
踊ってるだけで大丈夫　それをそっかそかって言って
Just dancing is fine, say "I see, I see" to that
お幸せに付いてとろ　何が正義なんかって思う
Let's melt into happiness, thinking about what justice is
生意気そうにガム噛んで　それもいいないいなって思う
Chewing gum cheekily, thinking "That's nice, that's nice"
テレスコープ越しの感情　どうかリズムに全部詰め込んで
Emotions through a telescope, please pack it all into the rhythm
せーの！
Ready, go!
踊ってない夜を知らない
I don't know a night without dancing
踊ってない夜が気に入らない
I don't like a night without dancing
踊ってない夜を知らない
I don't know a night without dancing
踊ってない夜が気に入らないよ
I don't like a night without dancing
気に入らない夜なんてうもう僕は知らない
I don't know any more nights I don't like
踊ってない夜がない夜なんてとってもとっても退屈です
A night without a night without dancing is very, very boring
一人二階で大丈夫　一人三階でも踊る
Alone on the 2nd floor is fine, I'll dance on the 3rd floor alone too
留守電でダンスする現状　これはチャンスなんかって思う
The current state of dancing to an answering machine, I think maybe this is a chance
カスタネットがほら　タンタタタンタタタタンタタタンタタ
Look, the castanets go tan-tata-tan-tata...
踊ってない夜を知らない人とかこの世に一人もございません
There's not a single person in this world who doesn't know a night without dancing
踊ってない夜を知らない
I don't know a night without dancing
踊ってない夜が気に入らない
I don't like a night without dancing
踊ってない夜を知らない
I don't know a night without dancing
踊ってない夜が気に入らないよ
I don't like a night without dancing
気に入らない夜なんてうもう僕は知らない
I don't know any more nights I don't like
踊ってない夜がない夜なんてとってもとっても退屈です
A night without a night without dancing is very, very boring
踊って生きるのはあなた、あなた。
Dancing through life is you, you.
ダンスは笑顔で回る。
Dancing turns with a smile.
踊ってない夜を知らない
I don't know a night without dancing
踊ってない夜が気に入らない
I don't like a night without dancing
踊ってない夜を知らない
I don't know a night without dancing
踊ってない夜が気に入らないよ
I don't like a night without dancing
気に入らない夜なんてうもう僕は知らない
I don't know any more nights I don't like
踊ってたい夜に揺らいでるなんて
Swaying on a night I want to dance
踊ってない夜を知りたい
I want to know a night without dancing
踊ってない夜が気に入らない
I don't like a night without dancing
踊ってない夜を知りたい
I want to know a night without dancing
踊ってない夜が気に入らないよ
I don't like a night without dancing
気に入らない夜なんてうもう僕は知らない
I don't know any more nights I don't like
踊ってない夜がない夜なんてとってもとっても退屈です
A night without a night without dancing is very, very boring
イェーイ！見てるかー！
Yeah! Are you watching?!
フー！お前ら頑張れー！
Whoo! Everyone, do your best!
ラプラス頑張れー！
La+ Darknesss, good luck!
お疲れー！
Good job!
戻ったよ、みんな！
I'm back, everyone!
頑張ったよ！
I did my best!
お疲れ様ですー！
Good job, everyone!
じゃ、お疲れ様でしたー。
Well then, good job.
待って待って！戻って戻って！
Wait, wait! Come back, come back!
終わりかー？
Are we done?
お疲れー！
Good job!
様子見疲れたよー。
Man, I'm tired.
こんな疲れたの初めてだわ。
I've never been this tired before.
みんな、Tシャツ見てよ！
Everyone, look at the T-shirt!
見て、これ見てください、これ。
Look at this, please look at this.
蛇足さん、ありがとう！
Dassoku-san, thank you!
ありがとう。
Thank you.
蛇足さん、出していただいてます。
Dassoku-san, thanks for joining us.
革命Tシャツや。
It's the Kakumei T-shirt.
そうだよ、みんなGTA V-RPじゃん、集まるの。
Yeah, everyone from GTA V-RP is here.
そうね、久しぶり。
Yeah, long time no see!
これ、足んないメンバーいない？
Wait, aren't there some members missing?
あー、まぁ、そいつちょっと忙しくてさ…
Ah, well, they were a bit busy...
しょうがないですよ、大人都合だよ。
It can't be helped, adult circumstances.
あたりにる、カワセ君、神成さん！
Atariiru, Kawase-kun, Kamito-san!
見てるかー！
Are you watching?!
頑張ってますよ、我々は。
We're doing our best!
ちょっとさ、革命結成順で思い出を語っていこう。
Let's talk about our memories in order of formation.
一番手はプードル。
First was Puudoru.
あ、そうなんだ！
Oh, is that so!
あ、そう、最初ね。
Yeah, at the very beginning.
プードルとあかくんがいて。
It was Puudoru and Akakunn.
で、その3人で釣りしようとしてたっけ？
And the three of us were going fishing, right?
そう、釣りしようって言ってた。
Yeah, we were talking about fishing.
そしたら、蛇足と烏有がいて。
Then Dassoku and Uyu were there.
あ、そうだったんすね。
Ah, is that how it was?
僕ら刑務所で出会って。
We met in prison.
悪いことしてるやん。
Doing something bad.
そう、悪いことしよーつって。
Yeah, let's do something bad.
蛇足知ってたから久しぶり！ってなったら、知らない人いて。
I knew Dassoku, so I said long time no see!
But then there was this stranger.
そう、ホント知らなかったよな、俺のことな。
Yeah, you really didn't know me back then.
だってお前、名前がリュウエっていっぱいいるじゃん、って。
Because there are so many people named 'Ryuue'.
女の子みたいな名前… 最低だよね。
A name like a girl's... That's terrible.
いやいや、わかんないよ。女の子かなーと思って。
No, I didn't know! I thought you were a girl.
それで誰彼構わずナンパして、ギャングやろうぜって。
So I tried to talk to everyone
and said let's start a gang.
最初「革命」って言ったのプードルだったの。
The first one who said 'Kakumei' was Puudoru.
あ、そうなの？ここで「革命」は出てたんだよ。
Oh, is that so? The word 'Kakumei' already came up.
で、ボスを押し付けられた。
And then the 'Boss' role was pushed onto me.
やっぱ蛇足さんがぴったり、ぴったり。
Dassoku-san was a perfect fit for it.
どうぞ、どうぞ、っつってな。
He was like, 'Go ahead, go ahead'.
で、そのあと、さんま。
And after that, Samma.
けんきさんとスタンミが同時ぐらい。
Around the same time as Kenki-san and Stan-mi.
スタンミが先で、けんきは面接に来た。
Stan-mi was first, and Kenki came for an interview.
面接なんや！俺、面接やったよ。けんきさん面接なん？！
An interview?! I did an interview.
Kenki-san did an interview?!
ちょっと面接した。
I did a bit of an interview.
えっ、お前同時だったの？
Wait, were you at the same time?
いや、違う違う、俺はちょっと早かった。
No, no, I was a bit earlier.
そうだよね、あんな安売りしないよね、だったらね。
Right, you wouldn't sell yourself short like that.
びっくりした、チェックしたら入ってたの、さんまが。
I was surprised! When I checked, Samma was already in.
で、「スタンミ」って誘おうとしたら入ってた。
And when I tried to invite Stan-mi, he was already in.
そっか、懐かしい。
I see, how nostalgic.
ちょっと違って、で、最後にあのアノ裏切り者。
A bit different... and then finally, that traitor.
やっぱり、烏有様だ！
As expected, it's Uyu-sama!
一番最後に入って、一番最初に裏切りました。
I was the last to join, and the first to betray us.
確かに。いや、申し訳ない。
That's true. Sorry about that.
どんな気持ちよ、お前、これやって。
How did you feel doing this?
非常に楽しかったです。
It was extremely fun.
最初寝てたしな。
You were sleeping at first, too.
第一回、寝てたから。留置所で。
The first time, I was sleeping. In the jail cell.
そんな感じで、来れる人、来ていただきました。
So, that's the group we have here today.
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
めっちゃ楽しいんだけど、これ！
This is so much fun!
スタンミが振り付け考えてくれて。
Stan-mi came up with the choreography.
コーチングしてたから楽しかったですけど。
I enjoyed coaching you guys.
ありがとう、来てくれて。
Thank you for coming!
みんなと一緒に歌えて嬉しかったです、ありがとう。
I was happy to sing with everyone, thank you.
またゲームとか、コラボしようね。
Let's collab on games again.
やろうやろう！
Let's do it!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
お疲れー！
Good job!
あっちにさ…裏切り者だから。
Over there... because he's a traitor.
待て待て待て！めちゃおもろいやんけ！
Wait, wait, wait! That's hilarious!
ということで、着替えました。
So, I've changed my outfit.
アウトフィット。ニューアウトフィット。いつもの服です。
Outfit. New outfit. It's my usual clothes.
今日はここまで見てくれてありがとうね。
Thank you for watching this far today.
ちょっとゲストがたくさん来たんですけど。
We had quite a lot of guests.
この後聴いてほしい曲があって。
There's a song I want you to hear next.
次はオリジナル楽曲です。
Next is an original song.
ホントにちょっとここまで不甲斐ない姿をたくさん見せてたんですけど。
I've shown quite a clumsy side of myself so far.
ちょっとセクシーな感じのオリジナル楽曲を聴いていただきたいと…
But I'd like you to listen to this sexy original song...
思います。恥ずかしい！頑張る！
I'm embarrassed! I'll do my best!
うわ、ばい、いきましょー！
Let's go!
drop candy
作詞・作曲・編曲 by ZERA
Lyrics/Composition/Arrangement by ZERA
死んだみたい
It's like I'm dead
まるで遺体
Just like a corpse
煩悩
Worldly desires
頭痛い
My head hurts
動けないの
I can't move
あたし
I
代わり映えしない
don't ever change
目眩
Dizziness
もう抜け出せない
I can't escape anymore
やめられないの
I can't stop
ドロップキャンディ
Drop candy
曖昧に
Vaguely
甘い honey
Sweet honey
あぁいいの
Ah, it's fine
愛の快楽狂い
Mad with the pleasure of love
幸せの一粒
A single drop of happiness
とろけて
Melting away
それは蜜の味
It's the taste of nectar
嗚呼 壊れちゃった
Ah, I've broken
欲しいの sweet sweet
I want it, sweet sweet
感じて flow
Feel the flow
恥じて crazy crazy
Ashamed, crazy crazy
奈落に堕ちて so
Falling into the abyss, so
あたしイィのしたい
I want to do something good
痛いくらいに堕ちて
Falling so far it hurts
now stop な 夜に酔いで
Now, getting drunk on the unstoppable night
もっと sweet sweet
More, sweet sweet
夢みたいに もう
Just like a dream, already
いいの 狂い狂い
It's fine, madly, madly
感じて slow
Feel it slow
苦いキッス
A bitter kiss
まるで怪物みたい
Just like a monster
まだ足りないみたい
It's still not enough
ドロドロに溶かして
Melting it all down
満たせないの
I can't be satisfied
変われないもう
I can't change anymore
歪む視界 以外
Everything but my warped vision
何もない苦悩
Is nothing but suffering
苦悩のナイトメア
A nightmare of suffering
ねぇあたし
Hey, I'm
まるで人間じゃないみたい
hardly human at all
マイドロップネス
My dropness
さあどうぞ
Now, here you go
曖昧に
Vaguely
honey my mind
あぁいいの快楽狂い
Ah, it's fine, pleasure crazy
幸せの一粒
A single drop of happiness
とろけた
It melted
それは蜜の味
It's the taste of nectar
嗚呼 壊れちゃった
Ah, I've broken
欲しいの sweet sweet
I want it, sweet sweet
痺れて flow
Numb, feel the flow
それは crazy crazy
That's crazy crazy
奈落に堕ちて so
Falling into the abyss, so
あたしイィのしたい
I want to do something good
痛いくらいに堕ちて
Falling so far it hurts
now stop な 夜に酔いで
Now, getting drunk on the unstoppable night
もっと sweet sweet
More, sweet sweet
夢みたいに もう
Just like a dream, already
いいの 狂い狂い 感じて flow
It's fine, madly feel the flow
苦いキッス
A bitter kiss
まるで怪物みたい
Just like a monster
まだ足りないみたい
It's still not enough
ドロドロな世界を抜け出したい
I want to escape this gooey world
my the sweet sweet candy
はっ！ラストの曲、どうだった？
Ha! How was the last song?
いぇい、気づいた？そう、新曲です。いぇーい！
Yay, did you notice? Yes, it's a new song. Yay!
やっただ！
I did it!
はい。ということで、3本目のシングル「drop candy」です。
Yes. So, that was my 3rd single, "drop candy."
えー、1年に1本のペースでオリジナル楽曲が出る
Um, original songs are coming out at a pace of one per year,
ということで、やっと出せました！ありがとねー！
so I finally got to release this one! Thanks everyone!
作詞・作曲・編曲は ZERA のお二人です。
The lyrics, composition, and arrangement are by ZERA.
エロいだろー！
Sexy, right?!
いっぱい聴いてくださいねー。
Please listen to it a lot.
はい！では、ここで最後の告知タイムを
Okay! Now, it's time for the final announcements.
させていただきたいです。ちょっとね、
I'd like to go over them. At the very end,
最後の方にはあの、いいものが見れるので、
you'll get to see something good,
ぜひ最後まで見ていってください。
so please stay until the very end.
では、詳細を1つずつ見ていきましょう！
Now, let's look at the details one by one!
ご紹介します。まずは、フルセット。
Let me introduce them. First, the full set.
これが全部です。
This is everything.
これが我輩の全て。
This is all of me.
じゃあ、1個ずつ見ていきましょう。
Now, let's look at each item.
1つ目、「ゲームが上手くなりそうなワイドラバーマット」。
First, the "Wide Rubber Mat that looks like it'll make you better at games."
じゃーん。イラストは さまてる先生で、我輩が、
Ta-da! The illustration is by Samateru-sensei, and it's me
あのデスクで銃を構えているイラスト。
holding a gun at my desk.
銃を構えている…あ、銃、銃、だあれ？あはは、待って。
Holding a gun... Oh, a gun, a gun, who's that? Haha, wait.
えーということで、イラストは さまてる先生で、
So, with an illustration by Samateru-sensei,
我輩がデスクで銃を構えている、かっこいいイラストです。
it's a cool illustration of me holding a gun at a desk.
ちょっと衣装違うんですけど、3年目でやっと出せた新衣装で
The outfit is a bit different, but I had it drawn in my new outfit
描いていただきました！
that I finally got in my third year!
サイズもね、これぐらいあるんで、ぜひお願いします。
It's about this big, so please check it out.
ゲームが上手くなるはず！次は、こちら。
You should get better at games! Next is this.
「ラプラス・ダークネスを強制的に笑わせることができるボイスキーホルダー」！
"Voice Keychain that can force La+ Darknesss to laugh"!
いぇーい！イラストはいつもの しろこ先生で、
Yay! The illustration is by the usual Shiroko-sensei.
えっとね、まあ笑ってるのが分かると、思うんですけどね、
And well, as you can see, she's laughing.
4パターン、笑い声を収録したんで、全部聴いてください。
I recorded four patterns of laughing, so please listen to them all.
あの、押すとね、ボイスキーホルダーを押すと、
When you press the voice keychain,
我輩が笑うという仕組みになってますんで、ぜひ聴いてねー。
I'll start laughing. That's how it works, so please listen to it.
つぎー！
Next!
「我輩の茶碗」！
"My Rice Bowl"!
ちょっと中二病だけど、名前は
The name's a bit edgy, but it's called
「総帥茶碗 〜Commander-in-Chief's Rice Bowl〜」。
"Commander-in-Chief's Rice Bowl."
ということで、我輩のデザインが入ったお茶碗になります。
So, it's a rice bowl with my design on it.
で、次。
And next.
「運命のダイス 〜Dice of Fate〜」！
"Dice of Fate"!
あ、まあこれはなぜか、まあちょっと、あの、
Ah, well, for some reason, um,
3個入ってるんです。なぜかね。
there are three in the set. For some reason.
よく知らないけど 3個ついてます セットで。
I don't know much about it, but it comes in a set of three.
良いですね 我がハイのイメージのモチーフです。
It's nice. It's a motif based on my image.
かっこいいですね。
It's cool, isn't it?
はい そして次はこちら！記念ボイス！
Yes, and next is this! Anniversary Voice!
えーっと 通話しながら寝落ちボイス
Uh, 'Falling asleep while on a call' voice...
ASMRです。
...it's ASMR.
まあ これもいいですよ。はい 次！フルセット購入特典 こちら。
Well, this is also good. Okay, next! Full set purchase bonus, here.
さまとる先生の描き下ろしポストカードで
A postcard newly drawn by Samatoru-sensei...
今回は箔押しとサインとメッセージが入っています。
...and this time it includes foil stamping, a signature, and a message.
えーとですね 前回前々回と2回連続でサイン
Well, I did hand-written signatures twice in a row last time and the time before...
直筆サインをやったらもう大変なことになってしまって
...and it became a huge ordeal...
本当に死んでしまったので
...and I really almost died...
今回はサインはお休みです。
...so I'm taking a break from signatures this time.
しかし 特典ボイスが2種類付きます。
However, it comes with two types of bonus voices.
ダイスゲームボイスと
'Dice Game Voice' and...
ダイスを振るときの掛け声ボイス。
...the 'Shouting when rolling the dice' voice.
ということで なんとなくわかるよね？
So, you can kind of tell, right?
今回ね お茶碗とサイコロがあるんだけど
This time we have a bowl and dice...
この2つがあれば あれができるよね？
...so with these two, we can do that, right?
そう チンチロだよね。
Yes, Cee-lo.
去年のホロフェスであの やりました 大人気のチンチロ。
At last year's HoloFes, we did it... the very popular Cee-lo.
我が輩が大無双したチンチロ みんなにもやってほしいなと思って。
The Cee-lo where I totally dominated. I wanted everyone to try it.
えっ 何何？チンチロのやり方がわからない？
Eh? What? You don't know how to play Cee-lo?
あーまあ そういう人もね いると思ったんで
Ah, well, I thought there might be people like that...
テストプレイの動画を用意してます。
...so I've prepared a test play video.
はい ということで
Yes, so...
こちらをどうぞ！
...please watch this!
へー なんでここでこれなん？
Heh? Why are we doing this here?
意味がわからない。
I don't understand the meaning.
なんで俺たちはこれをやらされる？
Why are we being made to do this?
やったことある？
Have you done this before?
いや 俺ないんだよ 今回初めてだから。
No, I haven't. This is my first time.
ちょっと教えを乞いたいんだよ。チンチロだもんね。
I want to be taught. It's Cee-lo, after all.
わからんか ルール。
Don't you know the rules?
わからんのですよ。
We don't know them.
ルールわからんか？
Don't you know the rules?
俺はわかるけどね やっぱりちょっと教えてもらいたいなってのはあるよね。
I know them, but I'd like to be taught a bit.
わかんない人いると思うんで ちょっと説明を。
I think there are people who don't know, so let's explain.
このチンチロのルールを説明するためだけにきました。
I came just to explain the rules of this Cee-lo.
非常にシンプルです。
It's very simple.
ルール: + それぞれ3回までサイコロ(3個)を振って出た日の役で勝負 + 強い役を出せば勝利
Rules: + Compete with the hand from rolling 3 dice up to 3 times each + Win by getting a stronger hand
サイコロ振って 役があります。
Roll the dice, there are hands.
役が強いほうが勝ち。
The stronger hand wins.
なるほど。なるほどね。
I see. I see.
なんで今日二人に 2負けで勝負してもらおうかなと。
So today, I'll have you two play until someone loses twice.
勝ち負けがないとさ 勝ち負けが起きたときのあの
If there's no winning or losing...
緊張感的なのが...
...that sense of tension when it happens...
キリつく何かが欲しい感はあるよな。
You feel like you want some sort of edge.
何もないとさ ただの運ゲーになっちゃうから。
Without anything, it's just a game of luck.
あーってなるだけだから。
It'll just be like, 'Oh well.'
何か 何か 何か！
Something, something, something!
じゃあ 負けた人が我が輩のモノマネで。
Then, the person who loses does an impression of me.
なんでだよ！
Why?!
やりましょう。
Let's do it.
こんなん負けたらもう致命傷や 大火傷確定や。
If I lose this, it's a fatal wound, guaranteed to be a huge embarrassment.
まあ もう役目終わったんで。
Well, my job is done.
いや おかしい！
No, that's weird!
嫌だ嫌だやりたくない！
No, no, I don't want to!
お前も道連れだ！
You're coming with us!
座れ！
Sit down!
3回振るうちに一人 誰から...
During the 3 rolls, one person, from whom...
逆の強さで一番弱かったやつがモノマネです。
The person who has the weakest hand based on reverse strength does the impression.
2負けにしよう。2回負けてもいいことにしよう。
Let's make it 2 losses. We'll make it so you can lose twice.
じゃあ 負けないぞ。
Then, I won't lose.
うわー！緊張する！
Uwaah! I'm nervous!
ションベン！
Pissing!
ションベンってヒフミのほうが下なん？
Is 'Pissing' lower than 'Hifumi'?
1 2 3出たらこれよりヤバイ。
If a 1-2-3 comes out, it's worse than this.
いくぞ 落とさないから俺は。
Here I go, I won't drop it.
おー 役ありやん。
Oh, you got a hand.
危なかった。
That was close.
俺も3回振ります。
I'll roll 3 times too.
ちょっと役とかよくわかんないんで教えていただきたい。
I don't really know the hands, so please teach me.
おい やめろ 俺に！
Hey, stop it, to me!
うわあ！
Uwaah!
俺の負けで終わりやん これ一個。
That's one loss for me then.
よしよし まだ1負け！
Alright, alright, only one loss!
うわー 強いよ！
Uwaah, it's strong!
あぶねー！
That was dangerous!
落とさないから俺は。
I won't drop it.
弱っ！
So weak!
行かせていただきます。まだ役なしがありますからね。
Allow me to go. There are still 'no hands' left.
うわー！
Uwaah!
嘘でしょ？
You're kidding, right?
いいぜ！
Nice!
リッチ！
Rich!
時間がないので早出し 蛇足が負けて最終戦へ
Fast-forwarding as time is running out. Hebijo lost, moving to the final battle.
完全版は後日公開！
Full version will be released at a later date!
決めようか。
Let's decide this.
うわー。
Uwaa.
行きます。
Here I go.
うわっ！しゃあ！
Uwa! Yes!
やった！やった！やった！
I did it! I did it! I did it!
我が輩やりました！
I did it!
危な。
That was close.
5！
Five!
ならんだ、ならんだ。5。
We tied, we tied. Five.
うわー、見てー、
Uwaa, look at that,
我が輩じゃん。
it's me.
我が輩じゃん、マジで。
It's really me.
最悪5以上。
Worst case, 5 or more.
すっごい震える。
I'm shaking so much.
行きます。
Here I go.
いやっ！
No!
やったー！
Yes!
最高！最高！
Best! Best!
勝った！
We won!
勝ったんだ！
俺たち勝ったんだ！
We actually won!
俺たちが勝ったんだ！
We were the ones who won!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
死ねー！
Take that!
やった！
Yes!
しゃー！
嬉しい...
I'm so happy...
我が輩だ...
It's me...
嬉しい...
I'm so happy...
お腹痛い。
My stomach hurts.
スタンミじゃぱんのラプラス・ダークネスのものまね。
Stanumi-japan's impression of La+ Darknesss.
待て。
Wait.
3。
Three.
2。
Two.
1。
One.
我が輩はラプラス・ダークネスである。
I am La+ Darknesss.
アハハハハ！
Ahahahaha!
（笑い/泣き）
(Laughing/Crying)
マジで良かった。
That was seriously good.
良かった。
That was good.
こんな大火傷するなんて。
I can't believe I bombed that hard.
カッコ良かった。
That was cool.
大火傷する。
I'm bombing hard.
なんてことをしてくれたんだホロライブ。
Look what you've done to me, Hololive.
なんてことをしてくれたんだ...
What have you done...
ホロライブ。
Hololive.
もう絶対ここ来ない。
I'm never coming here again.
一生ここに来ない。
I'm never coming back here for the rest of my life.
（笑い）
(Laughter)
俺はここに...
I'm never...
という感じでね、気軽に遊べるチンチロのグッズと
And just like that, the Chinchirorin goods you can play with casually,
チンチロ用のボイスも入っているので、
as well as Chinchirorin voices are included,
ぜひフルセットで購入して、
so please be sure to buy the full set.
お友達がいる人は我が輩の声まね、
If you have friends, please use my voice impressions
ものまねをかけて戦ってください。
to battle it out.
何そんなに嫌だったね？
Why was it so hated?
そんな、何でそんなみんな嫌がってたの？おい。
I mean, why was everyone hating on it so much? Hey.
「我が輩はラプラス・ダークネスだ！
“I am La+ Darknesss!
アハハ！」
Ahaha!”
という感じでした。
And that's that.
改めて、今日我が輩の誕生日、
Once again, on my birthday today,
みんな祝ってくれてありがとね。
thank you everyone for celebrating with me.
じゃ、バイバイ！
Well then, bye-bye!